what you're about to experience is a
你要经历的 是一个
free worldwide interactive broadcast
免费的全球互动广播
from Ontario Canada we broadcast live
来自加拿大安大略省，我们直播
every tuesday at seven p.m. eastern time
每个星期二，东部时间晚上七点
get your questions in join the community
加入社区，了解您的问题
chat room triple w category 5 TV or
聊天室三联类别5电视或
email us at live and category 5 TV and
给我们发送电视和5类电视和
now let's begin here's your host Bobby
现在让我们开始这里是你的主人鲍比
Ferguson welcome to number episode
弗格森欢迎来到剧集
number 168 of category 5 technology TV
5类科技电视的 168号
nice to have you here send him drunk
很高兴你在这里送他醉
useful mmm I'm Robbie Ferguson I'm Eric
有用的mmm我是 Robbie Ferguson我是Eric
Kidd Hillary's here with us as well hey
基德希拉里和我们在一起嘿嘿
hey hey everybody has a going world he's
嘿嘿，每个人都有一个 前进的世界
excited for another great show I know I
为我知道的另一场精彩表演感到兴奋
am well in a big hey out there the
我还有一个很大嘿那里的
category 5 TV universe yeah how's
5类电视宇宙是的如何
everybody doing nice to see you this
每个人都很高兴见到你
week this week we are we're still taking
本周一周我们 还在服用
qualifiers for that brand new a
这个全新的资格赛a
multi-function Center all-in-one printer
多功能中心多功能一体机
from Brother Canada and category 5 TV so
来自加拿大兄弟和5类电视
stick around for your chance to to
留下你的机会
qualify for that also we are going to be
我们也将有资格参加
looking at a simple technique that you
看着你的简单技巧
can use to make any image look like a
可以用来使任何图像看起来像一个
nice glossy button for use on the web
漂亮的光泽按钮在网络上使用
nice glossy button yeah we're going to
漂亮的光泽按钮是啊，我们要去
be starting up a new series over the
正在开始一个新的系列
next several weeks and this is kind of
接下来的几个星期，这是一种
our preliminary step to get started
我们开始的初步步骤
we're gonna be learning how to build a
我们要学习如何建立一个
website from scratch sweet so tonight
网站从零开始甜蜜所以今晚
we're going to be doing glossy buttons
我们将要做有光泽的按钮
just going to be something that we're
只是成为我们的东西
going to be tapping into that knowledge
将要利用这些知识
down the road Hillary what do you got
希拉里在路上你有什么
coming up in the news for us lots going
为我们提供了很多新闻
on in the world of techno
在技​​术世界中
g as always coming up in the newsroom
g总是在新闻编辑室里出现
microsoft accidentally announced a
微软意外地宣布了一个
couple months back that windows 8 would
几个月 前， 窗户8会
not be ready until 2012 and we'll tell
直到2012年才准备好， 我们会告诉你
you about it in case you didn't hear
如果 您没有听到，请告诉您
about the news previously in current
关于此前的新闻
news more than 70 sites alleged to be
新闻超过70个网站据称是
selling counterfeit goods or offering
销售假冒商品或提供
pirated content they've been shut down
盗版内容他们已被关闭
by the US government and its making the
由美国政府和它制作的
UK government feel that they want that
英国政府认为他们想要这样
amount of power to last passes acquired
获得的最后通行证的权力
the x mark service planet calypso
x标志服务行星calypso
introduces a new group of islands with
介绍了一组新的岛屿
plans to sell the in-game land and we
计划出售游戏中的土地和我们
know how much you all love gingerbread
知道你们多么喜欢姜饼
at this time of year so we'll talk about
每年的这个时候我们都会谈论
the latest release of android version
Android版本的最新 版本
2.3 stick around for the latest news
2.3留意最新消息
from the category 5 TV news room hmm I
来自5类电视新闻室嗯 我
love gingerbread love gingerbread
爱姜饼爱姜饼
alright so does gadget wisdom guru okay
好吧小工具智慧大师好吧
sounds great help thanks for being here
感谢在这里，感谢很棒的帮助
tonight now you I'm surprised you
今晚你现在我很惊讶你
actually made it tonight what's what's
实际上今晚它是什么样的
going on where you're at you will not
继续你在你身边的地方不会
believe this I have been trapped in my
相信我已被困 在我的 身上
house for two days and tomorrow will be
房子两天，明天将是
day number three because there is a
第三天，因为有一个
mother load of snow happening it's been
母亲发生的雪已经发生了
snowing non-stop for two days now
现在下雪不停两天
they've shut down the city and are
他们已经关闭了这个城市
declaring it in a state of emergency no
在紧急状态下宣布它没有
buses are running all the colleges
公共汽车正在运行所有的大学
universities elementary and high schools
大学小学和中学
in the second shut down so it's really
在第二次关闭所以它真的
crazy and I'm kind of scared I'm worried
疯了， 我有点害怕，我很担心
I'm I never make it back five welcome
我永远不会回来五欢迎
welcome to Canada we get no series you
欢迎来到加拿大我们没有系列你
can still broadcast through the wonders
仍然可以通过奇迹播出
of the web you have lots of food and
你有很多食物和网络
water we got lots of okay for now but if
水，我们现在有很多好处，但如果
this keeps up I don't know I don't know
这跟不上我不知道 我不知道
what happen yeah well hey thanks for
发生了什么，嘿，谢谢你
thanks for turning up tonight you can
谢谢你今晚可以参加
join us in the chat room category five
加入我们的聊天室类别五
dot TV be nice to have you there if you
如果你有点电视很高兴你在那里
have any questions for us and Hilary of
对我们和希拉里有任何疑问
course is joining us in the chat room as
当然是加入我们的聊天室
well and I guess you've got lots of
好，我想你有很多的
questions coming in as well great to see
提出的问题也很好看
everybody we are broadcasting tonight in
我们今晚要播放的每个人
a higher resolution and you're going to
更高的分辨率，你会去
notice if you're watching the RSS feeds
请注意，如果您正在观看RSS源
that we are stepping our way up to full
我们正在迈向全面
HD there you go there you go
HD你去你去那里
so we're looking forward to what the
所以我们期待着什么
next couple of months will bring with
未来几个月将带来
the increase in quality and certainly
质量的提高当然
let us know what you think already
让我们知道你的想法
seeing in the chat room that people are
在聊天室看到人们
noticing a difference in the quality of
注意到质量的差异
the feed and certainly most definitely
饲料，当然最肯定
in the RSS feeds you should notice as
在RSS提要中你应该注意到
well good to see everybody joining us in
很高兴看到每个人加入我们
the chat room lots of people there you
聊天室很多人在那里
can join us in the chat room it's on
可以加入我们的聊天室
freenode in the room category 5 or of
freenode在房间类别5或
course you can get there straight
当然， 你可以直接到达那里
through our website category five dot TV
通过我们的网站类别五点电视
and we'd love to have you join us in the
我们很乐意让你加入我们的行列
chat room and be able to say hey hmm
聊天室，能说嘿嗯
well hey I'm ready for you you're ready
嘿，我已经准备好了 你准备好了
for a question I'm ready all right how
对于一个问题，我已经准备好了
much snow what are we gonna get I just i
多雪我们会得到什么呢？
shoveled once already today and I've got
今天已经铲了一次， 我已经有了
this much in my driveway again yeah and
在我的车道上再次这么多是啊
put that much on top of my car again
把它放在我的车顶上
that's the thing yeah son around what
这就是耶和华的儿子
the heck whatever it's Canada welcome
无论加拿大欢迎什么，他们都会受到欢迎
Kennedy okay this is from John and this
肯尼迪， 这是来自约翰和这个
came in via email hiya I found your
来自电子邮件hiya我发现 你的
webpage through a link on the unraid
网页 通过一个关于unraid的链接
form watch the video where you built an
表格观看你建造的视频
a nun raid server from scratch very
一个尼姑突袭服务器从头开始
informative it's a project i'm looking
这是一个我正在寻找的项目
forward to undertaking soon the reason
很快前进的原因
for the message is because i can't
对于消息是因为我不能
register with your webpage and he's got
在您的网页上注册， 他就有了
a sad face that is colon and right
一个悲伤的脸， 是冒号和正确的
parenthesis okay left parenthesis I
括号好吧左括号我
filled out the form and hit send and get
填写表格 并点击发送和获取
an error back telling me the session has
回复告诉我会话有错误
expired cookies aren't enabled it's ever
过期的cookie没有启用它
I'm pretty sure the session couldn't
我很确定会议不会
have ended as i refresh the page filled
已经结束，因为我刷新页面填充
the form and hits and unless I'm sure
形式和命中，除非我 确定
than a couple of minutes and check these
超过几分钟 ，检查这些
cookies are set to accept in Firefox any
cookie设置为在Firefox中接受任何
ideas what I'm doing wrong look forward
想法我正在做错的期待
to hearing from you shortly with kindest
从你最善良不久听力
regards john cheers john what you well
尊敬的约翰欢呼约翰
there's a couple things first of all if
首先，如果有一些事情
you've already registered on the website
你已经在网站上注册了
then that's cool you should be able to
那你觉得很酷
login just clear your cache and
登录只需清除缓存即可
throughout all your cookies on the site
遍布网站上的所有Cookie
before you try to log in but because the
在你尝试登录之前，因为
site is under lockdown which means we're
网站处于锁定状态，这意味着我们
not accepting any new registrations at
不接受任何新的注册
the moment that's because we are
那是因为我们是
completely rebuilding the website from
完全重建网站
the ground up and part of that process
这是整个过程的一部分
is converting our entire user database
正在转换我们的整个用户数据库
over to a new format so in order to do
到了新格式，以便做到
that we had them well I had to make the
我们必须得很好，我不得不做
decision to completely lock down the the
决定完全锁定
website from new registration so if
新注册的网站如果
you're a new viewer are a new
你是一个新的观众是一个新的
registrants on our website category 5 TV
我们网站5类电视上的注册人
then it's possible that through this
然后它可能通过这个
transition period you may like if for
您可能喜欢的过渡期
example you had started the registration
例如，您已经开始注册
process at one point and then didn't
过程在一个点然后没有
respond to the email right away then it
回复电子邮件就那么
went into lockdown during that period
在此期间进入锁定状态
and so you're not able to get fully
所以你无法完全掌握
signed up so in a case like that you can
在你喜欢的情况下报名参加
pop me an email if you like live at
如果你喜欢住，请给我发电子邮件
category 5 TV with your user credentials
具有您的用户凭据的5类电视
and I'll go in and I can activate the
我会进去， 我可以激活
account manually but certainly as as
手动帐户，但肯定如此
we're in the process of developing the
我们正在开发中
new website it's going to be pretty
新网站会很漂亮
fantastic but it means no new
太棒了，但这意味着没有新意
registrations during this time so
在此期间注册
january first is the date that you want
1月首先是你想要的日期
to make sure that you're registered
确保您已注册
that's when the new website launches but
这是新网站发布时的情况
any time before then you can still use
在此之前的任何时候你仍然可以使用
the website obviously all the services
网站显然所有的服务
are available there and the lockdown
可以在那里和锁定
will not affect your ability to use
不会影响你的使用能力
category 5 s website it just means that
5类网站就是这个意思
you can't register as an insider at this
你不能在此注册成为内幕人士
time so sorry for the inconvenience for
时间很抱歉给您带来不便
those of you who are affected by that
那些受此影响的人
but it's one of those inevitable things
但这是不可避免的事情之一
where you know we got to make a decision
在哪里你知道我们必须做出 决定
where it's okay we're going to have to
在哪里， 我们将 不得不这样做
lock it down in order to make this
锁定它以便做到这一点
really happen so I'm very excited about
真的发生了所以我很兴奋
some of the new features that are going
一些正在准备的新功能
to be coming just gonna have to wait too
即将来临也必须等待
yeah well it's lit speaking of the new
是的，有点说 新的
website thank you to all the volunteers
网站感谢所有的志愿者
who have asked to become a part of the
曾要求成为其中一员的人
better process if you're interested in
如果你有兴趣，可以选择更好的流程
being a part of that process which means
成为这个过程的一部分意味着
just basically using the website before
只是基本上使用过之前的网站
it's actually ready reporting any kind
它实际上已准备就绪了
of issues through the betta forum and
通过betta论坛的问题和
also just submitting your ideas and
也只是提交你的想法和
potentially even how
甚至可能是如何
hang out with some of the copying and
和一些 复制一起出去 玩
pasting and the mundane tasks that have
粘贴和平凡的任务
to take place as much as possible i'm
我尽可能 地发生
using creating systems to automatically
使用自动创建系统
convert the mysql databases over to new
将mysql数据库转换为new
formats but sometimes there are things
格式，但有时有事情
that have to be copied and pasted
必须复制和粘贴
manually so that's if you are interested
手动，如果你感兴趣的话
in being a part of that process email me
作为该过程的一部分给我发电子邮件
live at category 5 TV just mentioned the
住在5类电视刚刚提到的
betta project or the the betta team in
betta项目或betta团队
the in the subject line of your email
在您的电子邮件的主题行中
i'll be great ok on the list well burn
我会在名单 上伟大确定 好烧
it with this new higher definition I'm
它有了这个新的更高的定义我
really taking the beating here they are
他们真的在这里受到打击
yeah it's inevitable sorry about that i
是的，我不可避免地抱歉
thought i would have warned you but look
以为我会警告你，但看
at all look at how clear the mug is
看看杯子有多清楚
which mug this mugger what that mug yeah
哪个劫掠这个劫匪什么那个杯子是的
you can certainly see every little green
你当然可以看到每一个小绿色
hair on the chin for sure well ok that
下巴上的头发肯定还好
said let's move on be kind to this man
说让我们继续对这个男人友好
yeah he's a good guy he's a good guy he
是的，他是个好人， 他是个好人
takes a lot from from you it takes even
需要很多，甚至需要你
more for me oh my goodness so I still
更多对我而言哦，我的天哪，所以我还是
want to know whether it really should be
想知道它是否真的应该
pronounced beta or better alpha beta on
发音为beta或更好的alpha beta
the betta page it says you say beta I
betta页面，它说你说beta我
say better ok which is mo betta nope
说好一点好吧，这就是mo betta nope
sorry I'll move on here we have a
抱歉，我会继续前进，我们有一个
question here clean bring ok yes and hi
问题在这里清洁带来 好的和喜
Robbie i have a lenovo edge laptop for
罗比我有一台联想边缘笔记本电脑
gig ram 500 gig hard drive came with
gig ram 500 gig硬盘随附
windows 7 and i would like to dual boot
Windows 7，我想双启动
with Ubuntu 1010 I would like to give
与Ubuntu 1010 我想 给
win 750 gig in the rest to a boon to I
在剩下的比赛中赢得750场比赛，给我带来福音
copied and pasted the partition table at
复制并粘贴分区表
the end also that Tina sorry I would
最后还有蒂娜对不起我会
like to know one do I partition the
想知道我要分区了
drive with win7 or gparted before
以前用win7或gparted开车
installation to do i create a swap
安装，我创建一个交换
partition manually or do I leave that
手动分区还是我离开
Lubuntu installer take care of that
Lubuntu安装人员负责这一点
three do I leave the recovery partition
三，我离开恢复分区
or delete it or backup to DVD kind
或删除它或备份到DVD种类
regards greg alright thanks Greg first
greg 好吧，谢谢格雷格先说
of all it really depends the answer to
这一切真的取决于答案
your question really is going to depend
你的问题真的会依赖
on how tech-savvy you are with partition
如何熟练掌握 分区技术
in a linux computer and the reason for
在linux计算机上的原因
that is because Boone too has a
那是因为布恩也有
fantastic automatic partitioning system
梦幻般的自动分区系统
so that you can just tell it you know
所以你可以告诉 它你知道
what use up use some of the free space I
什么用尽我使用的一些自由空间
think it's called just free space
认为它被称为自由空间
install to the free space on my windows
安装到我的窗户上的自由空间
7 system it'll automatically resize that
7系统它会自动调整大小
windows seven partition down create all
windows 7分区创建所有
the needed partitions within the freed
释放中所需的分区
space and you'd be good to go so that's
空间，你会很高兴这样的
that's really the end user super super
这真的是最终用户超级超级
easy way to do it I'm just looking at
简单的方法我只是看着
your partition table here just because
你的分区表只是因为
you mentioned it and included it so
你 提到它并包含它
we've got three partitions on the drive
我们在驱动器上有三个分区
right now one of them is a recovery
现在其中一个 是恢复
partition all right yeah yes I would
分区可以，是的，我愿意
leave the recovery partition because
离开恢复分区是因为
well here's here's what I would actually
好吧，这就是我的实际情况
do and this is the way I did it with my
做，这就是我用我做的方式
laptop I don't I actually don't ever use
笔记本电脑我不是，我实际上没有 使用过
windows 7 on my on my laptop but it did
Windows 7在我的笔记本电脑上，但确实如此
come with it so rather than throwing
来吧，而不是投掷
away that licensed copy of windows 7
远离Windows 7的许可副本
which maybe one day I'll want to you
也许有一天我会想要你
know throw that back on here do a
知道扔在这里回来做一个
partition use it for planet calypso or
分区用于行星calypso或
something on another partition for you
在你的另一个分区上的东西
in order to make it so that I still have
为了使它我仍然拥有
that option what I the first thing i did
这个选项是我做的第一件事
and the best thing that you can always
你可以随时做到最好的事情
do right off the bat is Hilary do you
Hilary你做的 就是蝙蝠
know do I know back up back up your
知道我知道吗备份你的
stuff she's looking at me like I was
她像我一样看着我
chatting in the chatroom know you want
在聊天室聊天 知道你想要的
to backup your stuff right away that's
立即备份你的东西
the first and foremost thing that you
你最重要的事情
want to do and in a case where you've
我想做你想做的事情
got your windows 7 partitions set up and
让你的Windows 7分区设置和
it's working on everything i would say
它正在努力我想说的一切
do a clone of that hard drive make a
做一个硬盘驱动器的克隆
make an image of that hard drive using
使用创建该硬盘的映像
something like clonezilla where you know
像你知道的clonezilla之类的东西
it's a free download you can download it
这是一个免费下载，你可以下载它
you can create an image of that of that
你可以创建 一个那样的图像
entire partition and then you can mess
整个分区然后你就可以搞砸了
around with it
与它相伴
we recreate the partition table if you
如果你重新创建分区表
ever need to if you ever want to revert
如果你 想恢复，就需要
back in time kind of thing so by
回到过去那种事情
creating a clonezilla part image of the
创建一个clonezilla部分图像
existing windows 7 system you've got
您已经拥有的现有Windows 7系统
your recovery partition you've got your
你的恢复分区你有你的
windows 7 partition all that stuff is
所有的东西都是windows 7分区
now built into that cloned image then
现在内置到克隆的图像中
boot up from your ubuntu CD and let it
从你的ubuntu CD启动并让它
do the partitioning itself if you unless
如果除非你做分区本身
you feel confident in doing the
你有信心做到这一点
partition table yourself i would say let
分区表自己我会说让
let linux take care of it for you if
让linux为你照顾它
you're reasonably novice as far as doing
就你而言，你是合理的新手
that kind of thing because you can break
那种事，因为 你可以打破
your ability to boot so always do have a
你就这么一直引导能力确实有
backup but essentially it makes it so
备份，但基本上它是如此
easy that I don't think you'll have any
很容易， 我不认为你会有任何
trouble so but that that image having
麻烦，但那个图像有
that image is a really great failsafe
那个图像是一个真正伟大的故障保护
because worst case scenario if
因为最糟糕的情况如果
everything breaks or down the road if
如果，一切都会在路上发生
you decide you know what I've one of the
你决定你知道我一直的一个
problems that you can run into in a
你可以 在 遇到问题
dual-boot environment is that windows
双启动环境就是windows
will degrade just like it normally would
会像往常那样降级
eventually it's going to get viruses
最终它会变成病毒
eventually it's going to have issues
最终它会有问题
that are going to you make you want to
这将告诉 你让 你想
reinstall windows whereas at that same
重新安装窗口，同时
time your Linux partition may be working
您的Linux分区可能正常工作的时间
just fine so you don't really want to
很好，所以你真的不想
have to go through a whole process of
必须经历一个完整的过程
wiping out everything you so creating
消灭你创造的一切
those images you could revert back to
那些你可以恢复的图像
previous points so but definitely have
之前的观点，但绝对有
an have an image then let down let going
有了一个图像，然后让放下
to do the partitioning for you first
先为你做分区
time at least down down the road if you
时间至少在路上如果你
want to try it yourself then I would
我想自己尝试一下
give it a go sounds like good advice is
给它一个听起来好听的 建议
that does that answer the question there
这样做可以 回答那里的问题
were three points there d let windows 7
那里有三点让窗户7
do it orgy part ed I would just do it
做它狂欢部分 我会做的
through the CD through boon to do you
通过CD通过恩惠做你
create the swamp partition again yeah
重新 创建 分区 沼泽 啊
just let it let it automatically do it
让它让它自动完成它
unless you feel confident enough you can
除非你有足够的信心，否则你可以
I did mine manually but that's because I
我手工做了我的，但那是因为我
want to control over how much space was
想要控制多少空间
allocated like specifically these days
这些天特别分配
though and with a larger hard drive
虽然和更大的硬盘驱动器
so it's not that big of a deal to to
所以这并不是什么 大不了的事情
make it exact right all right I hope
我希望，把它完全正确
that helps Greg thanks for thanks for
这有助于格雷格谢谢你
your question this is category 5
你的问题这是第5类
technology TV you'll find us online at
科技电视你会在网上找到我们
triple w category 5 TV nice to have you
三联类别5电视很高兴有你
here tonight and if you'd like to email
今晚在这里，如果你想发电子邮件
eric it's live a category 5 TV to get
埃里克它是一个类别5电视得到
your your questions in or of course in
你的问题在或课程
the chaplain right off of our website
我们网站上的牧师
category 5 TV on freenode cool all right
freenode上的5类电视很酷
all right well sounds like a little
好吧 听起来有点像
easier question hey Ravi when you get
更容易的问题嘿Ravi，当你得到
around to it could you update the
你可以更新它
portable mp4 and divx feeds for last
便携式mp4和divx直播
week's show I gotta I think I gotta ask
一周的表演，我想我得问
is anyone else thinking this how's your
是其他人在想这是怎么回事
eyesight tonight you notice this what
今晚你会注意到这一点
what are we any every time you read an
每次读书时 我们 都有什么
email you like okay okay well alright I
给你发电子邮件好吧好吧 好吧我
see an email here from Greg the reading
看看格雷格的电子邮件阅读
glasses are a little little smudgy I'm
眼镜有点脏， 我是
starting to get inside my personal
开始进入我的个人
bubble there every time you read me now
每次你现在读我的时候都会在那里泡
you know the camera guys want me to move
你知道相机的人要我 搬家
in oh boy okay notice he I cannot work
在哦，男孩好的通知他， 我不能工作
under these conditions but there is
在这些条件下，但有
candy you like a candy Hillary there is
糖果你喜欢糖果希拉里有
candy oh you got you got to warn me
糖果哦，你得警告我
would you like a candy Hillary okay oh
你想要一个糖果希拉里好吗哦
the gum it's very good yeah our
口香糖很好，是的，我们的
Christmas candy stash very festive go so
圣诞糖果藏品非常喜庆如此
you're not answering that question are
你没有回答这个问题
you what's that the one from our friend
你是我们朋友的那个人
David masters it is hey Robbie when you
大卫掌握它是嘿罗比当你
get around to it should I move in this
如果我搬进去，我就可以了解它
way could you update the portable entity
你可以更新便携式实体吗？
for and now he's talking while I'm
因为现在他正在和我说话
talking I cannot work under these
说话我不能在这些下工作
conditions Hilary well maybe I can maybe
条件希拉里也许我可以
if I get a raise oh so when you get
如果我得到加薪哦，所以当你得到
around to it could you update the
你可以更新它
portable mp4 and divx feeds for last
便携式mp4和divx直播
week's show thank
周的节目谢谢
Dave what was it that you called last
戴夫你上次打电话的是什么
week's show do you remember that was
本周的节目你还记得 那是
brilliant Eric's little nickname for our
杰出的埃里克为我们的小昵称
thrown together show when Halloween I do
扔在一起显示我万圣节的时候
not remember would I don't remember what
不记得我不记得是什么
I remember this seinfeld episode oh yes
我记得这个seinfeld插曲哦是的
it was kind of like yeah he didn't
有点像他没有
really have it there was no real water
真的有它没有真正的水
there's no no flash okay like yeah it
没有没有闪光可以，就像它
had a couple of humorous moments and but
有一些幽默的时刻，但是
Billy at the end of it you're just like
比利最后你就像
what did I just do for an hour so that's
我刚刚做了一个小时的事情
what you're missing there Dave yeah
你在那里失踪的是Dave耶
what's going to happen with the mp4 and
什么会发生mp4和
div X feet and the reason that last
div X脚和最后的原因
week's was not a priority as last week
本周的不是一个优先事项上周
was it was just after the baby was born
就在婴儿出生后
and it was a very different out of
这是一个非常不同的
format show a lot of fun granted I'll
格式显示我很有乐趣
say you got to see it but this did we
说你必须看到它， 但这就是我们
have too much fun day we always have fun
有太多有趣的一天，我们总是玩得开心
so the mp4 and div X feeds will be up to
所以mp4和div X将最多
date I'll do that for you in the
约会我会为你做的
meantime I would love to get an idea for
与此同时，我很想得到一个想法
how of how many people are actually
实际上有多少人
using the div X as well as the mp4 feed
使用div X以及mp4 feed
actively and rely on those because we do
积极地依靠那些因为我们这样做
have the h.264 feed which is the highest
拥有最高的h.264饲料
quality feed and you're going to get the
优质的饲料，你会得到的
full resolution high quality video
全分辨率高品质视频
through the h.264 div X and mp4 mp4 is
通过h.264 div X和mp4 mp4 是
still based on that old old old 320 x
还是基于那个老旧的320 x
240 I'm spec so it's very it's much
240我的规格是非常的
lower quality than the main feed but the
质量低于主要饲料但是
final size is still about the same so I
最终尺寸仍然大致相同所以我
as we build the new website we need to
当我们建立我们需要的新网站时
get a feel for whether or not Dave the
感受Dave是否
the mp4 feet is still advantageous to
mp4脚仍然有利于
keep that going because of the fact that
保持这一点，因为事实
it is such lower quality some people may
有些人可能会有这么低的品质
have devices that rely on it though so
虽然有这样的设备依赖它
that's why I'd like to know so if you
这就是为什么我想知道你的原因
could let me know about that and the div
可以让我知道这个和div
X I can understand that it's helpful to
X 我能理解它对你有帮助
have div xvideo so that will continue so
有div xvideo所以会继续如此
we'll we'll get that up to date for you
我们将为您提供最新信息
for sure
当然
evermind mentioned that they usually get
永远提到他们通常会得到
the mp4 a but I'd love to know if if
MP4的一个，但我很想 知道 ，如果
that's just because you subscribe to it
那只是因为你订阅了 它
two years ago and it's just the one that
两年前， 它就是那个
you've had downloading all this time
你一直都在下载
because understanding that that that
因为了解那就是那个
file is you know two to three hundred
文件你知道两到三百
megabytes and is only 320 x 240 maximum
兆字节，最大仅为320 x 240
resolution whereas you can get these the
分辨率，而你可以得到这些
480p and now the 720p feed that is about
480p和现在的720p饲料即将到来
the same size as far as the the file
与 文件 大小相同
download is but you're going to get that
下载但是你会得到它
from the h.264 feed so what that kind of
从h.264饲料那么那种
clarifies where where things are going
澄清事情的进展
with that but it just is like if you're
有了它，但它就像是你
going to download a two to three hundred
打算下载两到三百
mega file it might as well be super high
巨型文件它也可能超级高
quality as opposed to the old format
质量而不是旧格式
okay that's that's my wondering but
好吧那就是我的疑惑但是
we've kept that going over the years and
多年来我们一直坚持这样做
that I can certainly continue to do so
我 当然可以继续这样做
if people are actively using it for a
如果人们正在积极地使用它
purpose if there's a reason that you
目的，如果有你的原因
require that over the h.264 so let me
要求超过h.264所以让我
know live at category five dot TV ever
知道有史以来第五类电视直播
mine's going to give the h.264 files a
我要给h.264文件一个
try and let us know if it's going to
试着让我们知道它是否会发生
work on order on the media center judge
按媒体中心法官的命令工作
says I touched it I eat it but it's
说我触摸它我吃它但是它
wrapped in plastic jut you're easily
用塑料包裹包裹你很容易
distracted huh well he's good man what a
心烦意乱， 他是个好男人
bowl of candy in front of him nanodots
在他面前的一碗糖果nanodots
and candy anything that small and can be
和糖果任何小的和可以的
played with I mean you've done you've
和我玩意味着你已经完成了你
got Micah in here and you're sitting
让弥迦在这里，你坐着
here and well that was for Josh but I
这里和Josh但是我很好
wanted him to hear ready was in plastic
希望他听到准备好的是塑料
thanks John yeah way to go John thank
谢谢约翰，是的，约翰谢谢
you you're gonna get me fired dear me
亲爱的你，你会被我解雇
dear me okay all right we got enough
亲爱的我没关系，我们得到了足够的
time for another question before we we
我们之前的另一个问题的时间
get into the news if got one and of
如果得到一个，那就进入新闻
course if you got a question for us on
如果你当然有一个问题我们
the chat room category five dot TV love
聊天室类五点电视爱
to hear from you there
在那里听到你的消息
just calm yourself to you are you
让你自己平静下来吧
playing tonight well not with Chinese
今晚好好玩，而不是中国人
handcuffs that's what that's what good
手铐那是什么好事
gwg was suggesting for me to stop my
gwg建议我阻止我
fidgeting yes I'm didn't you and fidget
坐立不安我是不是你和烦恼
with those dude it doesn't matter what
和那些家伙一起无所谓
it you give him anything and he's
你给了他什么 ，他是谁
visiting with it I I don't know if you
与它一起访问我不知道你是否
noticed but we are and I mention it on
注意到，但我们是和我提到它
an earlier show but we put these pens on
早些时候的节目，但我们把 这些笔放在上面
the on the air they're great pens these
在空中它们是很棒的笔
are superantispyware com pens so you
是superantispyware com笔，所以你
know they're there one of our supporters
知道他们是我们的支持者之一
here at the show but we're not holding
在这个节目，但我们没有举行
these pens for the purpose of
这些笔的目的
advertising superantispyware we're
广告superantispyware我们是
holding these pens because the clackety
抱着这些笔，因为这个问题
ones he wouldn't stop playing with wow
那些他不会停止玩哇的人
so that's the story anyway back to the
所以这个故事无论如何回到了
tech but was he this hard to get along
技术，但他很难相处
with when you were here Hilary oh never
当你在这里希拉里哦，永远不会
just because you know he's wonderful
只是因为你知道他很棒
he's a good old boss we love having him
他是一个很老的老板我们喜欢和他在一起
around Oh Hilary oh boy I feel sweet
哦，希拉里哦，我觉得我很甜蜜
thanks buddy oh dear I don't like
谢谢哥们哦亲爱的我不喜欢
Hillary any more easily offended easily
希拉里更容易被冒犯
a good no seriously have you anything
一个好的没有认真对你有什么
tech to say I didn't realize it was here
科技说我没有意识到它在这里
for that perfect yeah well you need to
为了那完美，是的，你需要
say even ask you answer okay no no I'm
甚至要求你回答 好吧不，我不是
cattle all right so eight minutes to the
牛 好吧所以八分钟到了
news what are we gonna do eight minutes
新闻 我们要做八分钟
this question we should be able to cover
这个问题我们应该能够涵盖
it in eight minutes all right we have
我们在八分钟内就可以了
something from John steers hey John hi
约翰嗨嘿嘿嘿嘿
Robbie he has a new win7 64bit box and
罗比他有一个新的win7 64bit盒子和
is trying to understand if Ubuntu 64-bit
正试图了解Ubuntu是否为64位
is the way to go now ok well let's hit
现在是好的方式让我们好好玩吧
it looks like a multi-part is that it
它看起来像一个多的部分是它
does does it look like so let's hit each
看起来是这样的，让我们点击每一个
each thing at a time will you you and I
你和我一次一件事
you will be John I like I'll be Robbie
你会成为约翰我喜欢我会成为罗比
so you you asked the question so first
所以你你 问的问题，以便第一
thing is it the way to go first thing I
事情是 我 第一 件事 的方式
would check John is how much RAM is in
会检查John是多少RAM
that system and how much ram do you
那个系统和你有多少ram
eventually want to have
最终想拥有
reason being okay well there's two
理由很好，有两个
things but the RAM if you've got more
如果你有更多的东西，但RAM
than four gigs or if you plan to ever
比四场演出或者你打算永远
have more than four gigs you've got to
你有超过四场演出
go 64 bit plain and simple because it's
64位简单明了， 因为它是
windows seven though you could run into
Windows 7虽然你可能遇到
application and driver issues unlike
应用和驱动程序问题不同
Linux where if you you know if you
Linux如果你知道你是否在哪里
install something and it's only
安装一些东西，它只是
available is 32-bit and it just installs
可用是32位，它只是安装
the 32-bit lives and you're good to go
32位的生活，你很高兴
windows is going to be a lot more
窗户将会更多
problematic so boon to 64 bit on the
有问题所以对64位有利
other hand is going to give you a lot
另一方面是要给你一个不少
less trouble as far as compatibility
兼容性方面的麻烦较少
goes between 32 and 64 bit of course
当然在32到64位之间
you're going to possibly run into issues
你可能会遇到问题
with some things adobe is one of those
有些东西adobe 就是其中之一
companies that never seems to really
公司似乎永远不会真的
keep up with with other technology but
跟上其他技术但是
it says no support for 64-bit AMD
它表示不支持64位AMD
version of adobe flash well there is
版本的adobe flash很好
there if you use perfect boom to you can
如果你使用完美的繁荣，你可以
download it from perfect boom to
从完美的繁荣下载到
category five dot TV and i'll post the
五类点电视，我会发布
link in the show notes for episode 168
在第168集的节目笔记中链接
you'll be able to install flash no
你将能够安装闪存号
problem on 64-bit ubuntu with windows
带有Windows的64位ubuntu问题
seven though you can have a lot of
七，虽然你可以有很多
issues with compatibility with your 32
与32兼容的问题
bit software 32-bit drivers with linux
位软件32位驱动程序与Linux
with a boon to you're going to have its
带着恩惠， 你将拥有它
pretty much anything you can do on the
几乎任何你可以做的事情
32-bit you can do on 64-bit there's
你可以在64位上做32位
there we're just in this time that's
我们就在这个时候
exciting where everything just works as
令人兴奋的地方一切正常
well in the 64-bit has a dozen the 32
好在64位有十几个 32
with some exceptions of course but
当然有一些例外但是
generally speaking so I would say
一般来说，所以我会 说
definitely if you're going to if you're
如果你愿意的话，绝对是你的意思
going to eventually go more than four
最终将 超过四个
gigs of RAM I would absolutely go with
我绝对会选择RAM的演出
64-bit and personally I would probably
64位，我个人可能
do that anyways if my processor were to
无论如何，如果我的处理器是 这样做的 话
support it just because of the fact that
支持它只是因为一个事实 ，即
you're going to get the benefits of a
你会得到一个好处
64-bit OS so without getting into big
64位操作系统，所以没有进入大
details about about you know with the
约你知道与细节
speed benefits of 64-bit and whether the
速度优势64位和是否
application maybe you should touch on a
应用程序也许你应该触摸一个
little bit well you're going to find is
你会发现的有点好
eight minutes ago to news or well you're
八分钟前，新闻还是很好
going to find in the forums and stuff if
要去论坛找东西，如果
you if you really delve into it people
如果你真的深入研究了人们
going to be saying that oh well you can
会说，哦，你可以
install 64 bit but if your application
安装64位，但如果您的应用程序
is only 32 bit
只有32位
only going to run on 32-bit speeds and
只能以32位速度运行
stuff like this really kind of your
像这样的东西真的很像你的
relevant when it comes to just it works
只有它才有效
64-bit is extremely easy to get like
64位非常容易得到
it's just as easy to install and get
它就像安装和获取一样容易
working as your 32-bit now years ago it
在几年前它作为你的32位工作
was really difficult to get 64-bit going
真的很难得到64位
on your system now it's not so you might
在你的系统上现在不是这样你可能
as well do it if you're going to go over
如做它，如果你打算 去了
the four gig max on your RAM so ok ok so
四个演出最大您的RAM这样就 OK了 确定，所以
next question let's see well you're
下一个问题让我们看得很清楚
already touched idea 32-bit so all right
已经触及了32位的想法，所以没事
no go with the 64 surrounding the ISO on
没有围绕ISO的64
DVD or I am since I'm Johnny MBD burned
DVD或我，因为我是约翰尼MBD被烧毁
with win7 burner I did okay but can't do
用win7刻录机我做得很好但是做不到
anything with no flash player can't
任何没有Flash播放器的东西都不能
listen to my podcast and now when you
听我的播客，现在当你
say it can't do anything now first of
说它现在不能做任何事情
all the the iso for ubuntu is a CD iso
所有ubuntu的iso都是CD iso
not a DVD iso so you might try a cd-r
不是DVD iso，所以你可以试试cd-r
disc which may or may not depending on
光盘可能会或可能不会取决于
your hardware effect that your ability
你的硬件效果就是你的能力
to boot from that disc get a CDR burn
从该光盘启动获得CDR刻录
the iso make sure that the you know you
iso确保你了解你
should be able to boot from it and then
应该能够从它启动然后
boot up install it to your computer
启动将其安装到您的计算机上
first and then run perfect bhuntu or any
首先然后运行完美的bhuntu或任何
other system to install your Flash
其他系统安装你的 Flash
Player and you'll be good to go and now
玩家，你现在就好了
good guy also mentioning that of course
好人当然也提到了
there are boom two dvds and that's true
有两个dvds，这是真的
there's like the there's the DVD version
就像DVD版本一样
of ubuntu but that's very it's not as
ubuntu，但这不是那样的
common like that's not the one that
常见的不是那个
you're going to get just by default on
你将 默认获得
the ilume to website so i'm going to
ilume到网站，所以我要去
guess that you're probably using the the
猜你可能正在使用
CD iso but if it's the DVD then then
CD iso，但如果它是DVD那么
maybe i'm wrong in that comment so
也许我在那个评论中错了
thanks for the note there ok ok
谢谢你的笔记 好吧
therefore i'm reluctant to install ok
因此我不愿意安装好
what do you think of using seder SATA to
您如何看待使用seder SATA
ide connector so i can use my old win XP
ide连接器，所以我可以使用我的旧赢XP
system ok I've tried kvm switches but
系统好我已经尝试过kvm开关但是
they don't work ok so we're moving out
他们没有工作，所以我们搬出去了
of the Linux and 64-bit questions here I
这里有Linux和64位问题
think just to finalize those thoughts
想想最终确定这些想法
we're going to go 64 bit if we're going
如果我们要去，我们会去64位
to go over the four gig limit of this of
超过这个的四个演出限制
the 32 and whether we should be
32 和我们是否 应该
reluctant to install based on flash and
不愿意安装基于闪存和
I would say no because that's one
我会说不，因为那是一个
application it's necessary of course
应用它当然是必要的
like ask anybody who's using Ubuntu
比如问任何使用Ubuntu的人
Linux I've got a boon to 64-bit on any
Linux我对64位有任何好处
of my computers and I've got flash
我的电脑，我有闪光灯
working just fine using perfect boon to
使用完美的恩惠工作得很好
as the Installer so you won't have any
作为安装程序，所以你不会有任何
trouble there I don't think so it's more
在那里遇到麻烦我不这么认为
problematic than some other applications
比其他一些应用程序更有问题
because like I say adobe is not very
因为就像我说adobe不是很好
accommodating but but there are ways to
适应但但有办法
install it absolutely no problem what do
安装它绝对没有问题做什么
I think of SATA to ide adapters to run
我认为要运行SATA到ide适配器
your ide old hard drives as SATA hard
你的ide硬盘驱动器很难用SATA
drives on your computer is that what we
您的计算机上的驱动器就是我们的
mean are we going the other way around
我们走的是另一种方式
on your old win XP system well from what
在你的旧赢XP系统上，从什么
i've read say that ID connectors should
我已经读过ID连接器了
allow me to use my XP system with a CA
允许我将我的XP系统与CA一起使用
divided need drivers so you want to
分开需要司机所以你想要
write beyond the solar action we're
写下我们的太阳能行动
taking an SATA hard drive and making it
拿一个SATA硬盘并制作它
an ide hard drive so you're taking a
一个ide硬盘，所以你 要拿一个
drive that's designed to carry 300
驱动器设计用于携带300
megabytes per second as its throughput
每秒兆字节作为吞吐量
and you're taking it down to 133
你把它降到了133
megabytes a second no his XP is on an
兆字节一秒没有他的XP在
ide drive right he wants to hook it up
他想把它连接起来
to a seder put it in a computer with
一个家庭把它放在一台电脑上
SATA yeah so the opposite would be true
SATA是的，所以相反的情况是真的
then but you'd be taking a drive that is
然后，你将采取一个驱动器
166 megabytes a second it's bus speed
每秒166兆字节的总线速度
and running it through a computer that's
并通过计算机运行它
designed to take 300 megabytes per
设计为每个300兆字节
second possibly six if it's SATA 3 right
第二个可能是六个，如果SATA 3是正确的
so in that case you won't be getting the
所以在这种情况下你不会得到
performance the either way whichever
以任何一种方式表现
whichever way is true you're not going
无论哪种方式都是如此，你就不会去
to get the performance of a true SATA
获得真正SATA的性能
hard drive plain and simple those those
硬盘简单而简单那些
adapters are excellent for like I would
适配器非常适合我喜欢
use them if I have an old ID hard drive
如果我有一个旧的ID硬盘驱动器，请使用它们
and I need to transfer the data on to
我需要将数据传输到
I unraid server for example move it on
我unraid服务器例如移动它
to another device whether you'd want to
到另一个设备是否你想要
use that as your as your system hard
用它作为你的系统很难
drive or not using an adapter it's going
驱动或不使用适配器
to degrade your performance cut your
降低你的表现削减你的
speed of your hard drive in more than
你的硬盘速度超过
half of what I'm just wondering if maybe
我只是想知道是否可能的一半
and I could be wrong sure that john
约翰，我肯定错了
wants to maybe be able to run a third
想也许能够 运行第三
system he's got the win 7 computer he's
系统他得到了Win 7的电脑 他
got but all right the same computer just
我只是在同一台计算机上
you know maybe I'll Apple boot / hello
你知道也许我会Apple启动/ 你好
and I could be wrong guys but that's
我可能是错的家伙，但那是
what I'm thinking you want still to have
我在 想你还想拥有什么
as XP computer XP on that old hard drive
作为那个旧硬盘上的XP电脑XP
yeah is the overdrive okay so so same
是的，过载是好的，所以同样如此
thing still goes but XP you're asking
事情还在继续，但你问的是XP
about using an adapter so I have to
关于使用适配器所以我必须这样做
assume that the XP drive is coming out
假设XP驱动器即将推出
of another computer and you can't take a
另一台电脑，你不能拿一个
windows XP drive and move it from one
Windows XP驱动器并从一个移动它
computer to the other because it's just
计算机到另一个，因为它 只是
going to growers is going to be that's
去种植者 就是这样
going to blue screen as soon as you turn
转弯后立即进入蓝屏
it on you can do what's called a repair
它可以做你所谓的修复
install but at that point you might as
安装，但在那时你可能会
well have just reinstalled it on another
好吧刚刚在另一个上重新安装它
another hard drive that actually uses
另一个实际使用的硬盘
the the proper bus SATA so I would
适当的总线SATA所以我会
probably stay away from that to be
可能远离那个
honest with you if you want to have XP
如果你想拥有XP，请跟你说实话
as a triple boot system throw it on
作为一个三重引导系统扔它
another partition or install another
另一个分区或安装另一个
hard drive that's SATA and just do a
硬盘驱动器是SATA，只是做一个
clean install of a nice clean windows XP
干净安装一个漂亮干净的Windows XP
installation yeah you could run
安装是的你可以跑
terabytes boot it boot it ng for triple
terabytes启动它启动三倍
booting another one another boot loader
另一个启动另一个启动加载器
that's easy for now this is kind of
现在 很容易 就是这种情况
getting away from that stuff but
远离那些东西但是
something you might want to look at is
你可能想看的东西是
oh now I'm going to forget the name
哦，现在我要忘记这个名字
it's one of Akron esas products disk
它是Akron esas产品磁盘之一
director or something like that I was
导演或类似的东西
right acronis disk director is a
正确的acronis磁盘导演是一个
commercial application that's one that's
商业应用就是这样的
pretty neat as far as doing multiple
做多次相当整洁
partition booting it makes it really
分区启动它真的
really easy to repartition your
真的很容易重新分配你的
harddrive and expert level yeah it's
硬盘 和专家级别是的
cheap 4999 what was the other one that
便宜4999那是另一个
was recommended there in the Chapman um
是在查普曼那里推荐的
terribly ng wasn't it by terribly
可怕的不是非常糟糕的
terabytes boot it ng who did the next
terabytes引导谁做了下一个
generation see it's also commercial it's
一代看到它也是商业的
3495 I haven't used that one so I
3495 我没用过那个，所以我
couldn't say whether or not it's it's as
不知道它是否如此
good as Akron us but maybe compare the
好像阿克伦我们，但也许比较
feature set between between the two
两者之间的功能设置
that's all american dollars this is all
这就是所有的美元
relative pretty close of here okay and
相对非常接近这里好吧
yeah it's not like a year ago when it
是啊， 不像一年前 ，当它
made a difference okay I hope that helps
有所作为， 我希望有所帮助
did we cover everything for John I
我们是否为约翰一世报道了一切
thought four was John right yeah yeah
以为四是约翰对，是的，是的
John and Dallas hey dells right John let
约翰和达拉斯嘿嘿小伙子约翰让
us know if I haven't been clear on
如果我不清楚，我们知道
something or if if you need any better
某事或如果你需要更好的话
explanations about any of that stuff and
关于任何这些东西的解释
then certainly send us more information
然后肯定给我们发送更多信息
about your your specific requirements
关于您的具体要求
what it is that you want to do and i'll
你想做什么，我会做什么
i'll be happy to to give you a hand with
我很乐意帮助你
that if i can all right so that that
如果我可以这么做那么
pretty much takes us there we're ready
几乎把我们带到那里我们准备好了
yeah how's it going hell oh it's going
是的，它是怎么回事哦，它会发生的
and I got plenty of news for you coming
我有很多新闻要你来
live from the category 5 TV news room
住在5类电视新闻室
while not new news for those of you who
虽然对你们这些人来说不是新消息
didn't hear the first time a posting on
没有听到第一次发帖
Microsoft's Dutch site suggests that
微软的荷兰网站暗示了这一点
will have to wait until 2012 for the
将不得不等到2012年
next release of Windows
Windows的下一个版本
microsoft declined to comment and the
微软拒绝发表评论
message was rapidly deleted but was
消息被迅速删除但是
grabbed by ina fried at cnet and a host
在cnet和主持人身上被油炸了
of other bloggers the post celebrating
其他博主的帖子庆祝
the first birthday of windows7 said that
windows7的第一个 生日就是 这样说的
microsoft was hard at work on windows 8
微软很难在Windows 8上工作
but the release was about two years away
但是发布大约两年了
in place of the offending paragraph on
取代违规段落
the Dutch site it was revised to say
修改后的荷兰网站说
that windows 7 service pack 1 is
Windows 7 Service Pack 1是
currently in testing and will be
目前正在测试并将
released in the first six months of next
在接下来的前六个月发布
year Microsoft may still be an expert in
一年微软可能仍然是专家
making cash but is perceived as failing
赚钱但被认为是失败的
to innovate or to cash in on that
创新或赚钱
innovation compared to a renewed Apple
与更新的 Apple相比，创新
and ever-expanding google windows 8 will
和不断扩大的谷歌Windows 8将
have a heavy burden to carry CEO of
承担首席执行官的沉重负担
Microsoft Steve Ballmer said would be
微软史蒂夫鲍尔默表示会
the company's riskiest ever release more
该公司风险最大，发布更多
than 70 sites alleged to be selling
超过70个涉嫌销售的网站
counterfeit goods or offering pirated
假冒商品或提供盗版
content have been shut down by the US
内容已被美国关闭
government this action was taken by the
政府采取了这一行动
Immigration and Customs Enforcement
移民和海关执法局
Agency part of the u.s. department of
美国部门的代理部门
homeland security domain seeds include a
国土安全域种子包括a
bit torrent search engine music download
比特洪流搜索引擎音乐下载
sites and shop selling fake designer
网站和商店出售假设计师
clothing many of the sites who lost
服装很多遗失的网站
their domains have continued training
他们的领域继续培训
via alternate addresses anyone who tried
通过备用地址尝试任何人
to visit these these pages was
访问这些页面是
confronted by a screen saying that the
面对一个屏幕说，该
domain have been taken over by IC which
域名已被IC接管
quoted us laws on copyright infringement
引用了我们关于版权侵权的法律
and traffic and counterfeit goods the
而交通和假冒商品的 ，
action comes at the UK serious and
行动来自英国严重和
Organised Crime Agency and they see
有组织犯罪机构和他们看到
similar powers over dot uk' domains and
类似的权力比点uk'领域和
it seems are involved in criminal
它似乎涉及犯罪
activity LastPass which is a
活动LastPass是一个
cross-platform password manager has
跨平台密码管理器有
acquired X Mars and a cross-platform
收购了X Mars和一个跨平台
bookmark tab history and password sync x
书签标签历史记录和密码同步x
marks will join last passes freemium
标记将加入最后一次通过免费增值
model the browser plug-in and most of
模拟浏览器插件和大部分内容
what users are used to will remain but
用户习惯的东西会留下来
new features will be available including
将提供新功能， 包括
an iphone and android app those features
一个iPhone和Android应用程序的那些功能
will be part of the USD 12 a year
将成为每年12美元的 一部分
premium package you can get both
高级套餐，你可以得到两者
LastPass and x marks premium bundle
LastPass和x标记高级捆绑
together for us do $20 us left the two
一起为我们做$ 20个美国留下两个
services will continue to requires
服务将继续需要
separate downloads
单独下载
we administered through two distinct
我们管理两个截然不同的
extensions and websites although there
虽然有扩展和网站
are plans to integrate them in the
是计划将他们整合到
future since the introduction of in-game
自从推出游戏以来的未来
vehicles players in the entropia
在entropia的车辆运动员
universe planet of calypso have been
calypso的宇宙星球已经
able to explore like never before flying
能够像飞行前一样探索
over predators or speeding past them on
掠食者或超速驾驶它们
land now my dark is providing even more
土地现在我的黑暗提供更多
land to explore with the introduction of
土地探索与介绍
the Medusa head group of islands an
美杜莎群岛群岛
all-new area on planet calypso located
位于calypso星球上的全新区域
between you Doria and I'm a thorough I'm
你和多丽亚之间我是 一个彻底的我
a thorough I hope I'm saying that right
彻底我希望我说得对
imma Sarah and etheric continents for
imma Sarah和以太大陆
stop from looking to invest in in Game
停止寻找投资游戏
real estate the new land area goes up
房地产新的土地面积上升
for sale in the in-game auction on
在游戏中拍卖
December 13th not ready to invest no
12月13日还没准备好投资没有
problemo you can explore Medusa's head
你可以探索美杜莎的头脑
now on planet calypso by downloading the
现在通过下载星球卡里普索
game absolutely free from cat5 TV /
游戏完全免费来自cat5 TV /
Calypso yesterday google released a
Calypso昨天谷歌发布了一个
software development kit for android 2.3
用于android 2.3的软件开发工具包
known as gingerbread how it for the
被称为姜饼如何为它
holiday season we will also announce
假期我们也会宣布
their latest developer phone the samsung
他们最新的开发者手机三星
nexus s which will launch with
将推出的nexus s
gingerbread installed on it gingerbread
姜饼上安装姜饼
will feature user interface refinements
将提供用户界面改进功能
improve power management and integrated
改善电源管理和集成
internet as IP calling the software
互联网作为IP呼叫软件
development kit adds enhancements for
开发套件增加了增强功能
game development and multimedia get
游戏开发和多媒体获取
these full stories a category 5 dodge TV
这些完整的故事是5类道奇电视
/ newsroom the category 5 da TV news
/新闻室5类电视新闻
room is researched by roy w nash with
房间由roy w nash研究
contributions from gadget wisdom guru
小工具智慧大师的贡献
back of ferguson and our community and
弗格森和我们的社区和
viewers if you have a story thanks
观众，如果你有一个故事谢谢
worthy of on-air mention email us at
值得播出的电子邮件给我们发电子邮件
news room at category 5 TV but a
5类电视新闻室但是
category 5 kami newsroom I'm Hillary
5类kami新闻室我是希拉里
rumble
隆隆
category 5 TV is brought to you in part
5类电视部分带给您
by planet calypso this massive
由行星calypso这个巨大的
multiplayer online game is available as
多人在线游戏可作为
a free download from cat five dot TV /
从猫五点电视免费下载
Calypso now once you've got it
卡里普索现在有了它
downloaded and installed on your Windows
下载并安装在Windows上
computer make sure you say hi and
电脑一定要打个招呼
there's something for everyone here on
这里有适合每个人的东西
planet calypso from hunting to mining
行星calypso从狩猎到采矿
crafting and just plain socializing and
制作和简单的社交和
having fun with your friends you can
和你的朋友一起玩，你可以
download it for free at cat five dot TV
在cat five dot TV免费下载
/ Calypso if you're a linux user like
/ Calypso，如果你是一个像Linux的用户
myself of course this makes it worth the
我当然这是值得的
dual boot cat five dot TV / calypso i'll
双启动猫五点电视/ 卡里普索我会
see you on planet calypso this is
在calypso星球上见到你
category 5 technology TV you'll find us
您会找到我们的5类技术电视
online at triple w category five dot TV
网上三联五类五点电视
hillary was saying there during the
希拉里在那期间说
commercial break that somebody was at
有人在的商业休息时间
the door going Hillary all right all
朝门口走去希拉里没事
right money is everybody more you know
正确的钱是你知道的更多人
whatever roommates more her picture no
无论室友多，她的照片都没有
was there she is hopefully she'll be
在那里，她希望她会成为
back hopefully she'll be she's out to
希望她能成为她的一员
get water and food and candles and stuff
得到水和食物，蜡烛和东西
shovel this out it's your turn sir
铲掉这是你的转身先生
shovel oh my goodness alright so in a
铲子哦，我的天哪，好吧
couple of minutes we are going to be
几分钟我们将会是
looking at how to create some buttons
看着 如何创造一些按钮
for our upcoming website so you want to
对于我们即将推出的网站， 您想要
stick around for that we're gonna be
坚持到底，我们会成为
using free software the GIMP GNU image
使用免费软件 GIMP GNU图像
manipulation program so stick around in
操纵程序如此坚持
the meantime here to answer your
在此同时回答你的问题
questions you can pop me an email live
问题你可以直接给我发电子邮件
at category 5 TV or of course you can
在5类电视或当然你 可以
also join us in the chat room at triple
也加入我们三人聊天室
w category 5 TV hold are you all right
w类别5电视 举行你 没事
all right well this is ready for some
没事嗯， 这是准备好一些
more question I'm not sure this is
更多问题我不确定这是什么
actually a question or this is from femi
实际上一个问题或者这是来自femi
murphy me hi Robbie I have updated feed
墨菲我喜欢 罗比我 已经更新了饲料
pixel comm check it out
像素通讯检查出来
dot dot all right be pixel book already
点点可以是像素书了
go there feed pixel calm there we go and
去那里喂像素平静我们去
then the new site looks fantastic what
然后新网站看起来很棒
this is is it's a it's a free podcast
这是一个免费的播客
directory and online player so you can
目录和在线播放器，所以你可以
catch your podcast directly through this
通过 此直接捕捉您的播客
system through the web so you're able to
系统通过网络，所以你能够
get your podcast from video podcast I
从视频播客中获取您的播客
mean from pretty much anywhere just
意味着来自几乎任何地方
through your web browser pretty cool and
通过您的网络浏览器非常酷
they've developed their own player
他们开发了自己的球员
everything it's it's very very cool so
这一切都非常非常酷
like leads into can we go and watch cat
喜欢引导我们可以去看猫
five oh yeah yeah very cool category
五哦是的是非常酷的类别
five of course is on feed pixel calm but
五个当然是关于饲料像素平静但
you definitely check it out feed pixel
你肯定检查出饲料像素
calm it's a start up service so you I've
冷静它是一个启动服务所以你我
noticed that over the past few months
注意到过去几个月
there's been constant and continual
一直持续不断
growth of the service so you'd want to
服务的增长，所以你想要
check that out I'll include a link in
检查一下， 我将包含一个链接
the show notes of episode number 168 as
第168集的节目笔记为
well and if your visit perhaps our
好吧，如果你的访问也许是我们的
visitors want to know what is a podcast
访问者想知道什么是播客
you can go to the following link that
你可以转到以下链接
you're going to show it well you're not
你要表现 得很好，你不是
hey well I'm feed pixel calm there is a
嘿，我喂的像素平静有一个
link for what is a podcast
什么是播客的链接
so yeah you can go through the menu I'd
所以，是的，你可以通过我的菜单
early versus there yeah but i'd
早期与那里是的但我会
encourage everyone to to check it out
鼓励大家去检查一下
yeah those femi murphy me from Sweden
是的，那些来自瑞典的 femi 墨菲我
thanks for the email very cool all right
谢谢你的电子邮件非常酷
good time tomorrow absolutely I
我明天的好时光绝对是我
shouldn't be asking I should just jump
不应该问 我应该跳
in and you can Bobby if you have to well
如果你必须好的话 ，你可以和Bobby 一起
this one is from Peter Peter Lewis and
这个是彼得彼得刘易斯和
keep here dear Robbie I'm invading your
亲爱的罗比，我正在入侵你
space bubble congratulations to you both
太空泡沫祝贺你们俩
on the birth of your new baby that was
关于你的新生儿的诞生
not our baby that was Robbie in and
不是我们的宝贝，而是罗比
Becca yeah doesn't work that way give
贝卡耶不工作，这样让
our best wishes to Becky i watch your
我们向Becky致以最诚挚的祝福
show regularly every week and enjoy it
每周定期展示并享受它
very much it is quite late around
非常晚了
midnight gmt so what said gmt what time
午夜gmt所以gmt什么时候说的
is that zero is Greenwich Mean Time yeah
是格林威治标准时间是零是啊
okay like off of us from five hours five
好吧，就像我们五小时五的时间一样
hours four hours depending on date yes
小时四小时，具体取决于日期
exactly so I try to stay awake to listen
确切地说，我试着保持清醒倾听
to it I find your format very relaxing
我发现你的格式很轻松
and very informal especially last week
非常非正式，尤其是上周
actually he didn't say that but keep up
实际上他并没有这么说 ，而是跟上了
the good work for next year please let
明年的好工作请让
eric know i don't live very far from
埃里克知道我不住在很远的地方
Bushmills exactly five kilometers wow
布什米尔斯正好五公里哇
wow you know you can send here from
哇，你知道你可以从这里发送
bushmills distillery i have also seen on
我也见过的 bushmills酒厂
TV that there is a new whiskey liquor
电视那里有新的威士忌酒
called ballycastle we don't live too far
我们称之为巴利卡斯尔并不住得太远
from there either you know what there
从那里要么你知道那里
could be a road trip involved here do
可能是这里涉及的公路旅行吗
you have a guest room because eric has
你 有一间 客房，因为埃里克有
happened so much yeah we don't lose
发生了这么多，是的，我们不会失去
superb okay it may not be our
棒极了好吧它可能不是我们的
ballycastle which in ireland and part of
在爱尔兰和部分地区的巴利卡斯尔
UK as i know there is one in the
我知道英国有一个
Republic vironment as well at the moment
共和国的环境也在 此刻
we have had some quite heavy snow with
我们有一些相当大的雪
icy conditions yeah us too however it is
冰冷的条件是的，但是我们也是
not as bad or as cold as you get in
没有你进来那么糟糕或冷
Canada regards to all best wishes for
加拿大向所有人表示最良好的祝愿
happy Christmas in New Year 2011 oh PS
2011年新年快乐圣诞节哦PS
lives in a small village called der
住在一个名为der的小村庄里
vaart which is between ballycastle and
在巴利卡斯尔和巴利卡斯之间的vaart
bushmills it can be found in google maps
bushmills它可以在谷歌地图中找到
well Peter I will be google mapping that
好吧彼得我将谷歌映射
location very cool so
位置非常酷
like honestly not like no no offense or
老实说不喜欢没有冒犯或者
anything but der valk sounds very
除了德瓦尔克以外的任何东西
Klingon ish to me is it just me nope
克林贡恩，对我来说，这只是我的罪恶
sorry that's that's all converts a
对不起，这就是所有的转换
Vulcan yea sorry I'm is der Valk a
Vulcan是的，对不起，我是Valk a
Klingon word like why does that seem
克林贡语单词就像为什么， 似乎
just sounds that way gadget wisdom guru
只是听起来像小工具智慧大师
can can let me know I don't know I like
可以让我知道我不知道 我喜欢
the idea of der valk definitely sounds
德瓦尔克的想法绝对听起来
like a great place it does indeed oh you
就像一个伟大的地方，它确实哦，你
want more ok well there is more I'm
想要更好，我还有更多
watching the chat room here lots of lots
在这里看聊天室很多
of conversations going on and of course
谈话正在发生，当然
if you have any questions for me
如果您对我有任何疑问
mentioned in the chat room gad will is
在聊天室中提到的gad会是
saying that if they do have a guest room
说如果他们有一个客房
hopefully they will include a dictionary
希望他们会包括一本字典
that includes proper pronunciations
包括正确的发音
alright well this is from Philip
好吧，这是来自菲利普
Andersson hey Philip dear category 5 and
安德森嘿菲利普亲爱的 5 和 5 类
Robbie guess that makes Hilary in me
罗比猜测这让希拉里在我身边
category bug it does on yeah and the
它上面的类别错误是啊和
rest of our research team if anybody
如果有人 ， 我们的其他研究团队
finds UAC annoying and they turn it off
发现UAC很烦人，他们把它关掉了
then I would like to say do not turn it
那么我想说不要打开 它
off because of that there is a solution
因为这有一个解决方案
which I would like to share with you all
我愿与大家 分享
it's called UAC trust shortcut 1.0
它被称为UAC信任快捷方式1.0
notice that the new version might soon
注意新版本可能很快就会出现
be released in the IT knowledge 24.com
在IT知识24.com中发布
community which has made this tool for
为此制作此工具的社区
Windows Vista and Windows 7 users please
请Windows Vista和Windows 7用户
note the update about a new version of
请注意有关新版本的更新
IT knowledge 24 coms next UAC trust
IT知识24 coms接下来UAC信任
shortcut comes from their twitter
快捷方式来自他们的推特
updates let's continue the tool is very
更新让我们继续使用该工具
awesome and does the job if you have any
太棒了 ， 如果有的话可以 胜任
program which you trust and by default
您信任的程序，默认情况下
prompts with UAC dialogue every time you
每当你提出UAC对话时都会提示
want to run it then use UAC trust
想要运行它然后使用UAC信任
shortcut 1.0 and make a new shortcut
快捷方式1.0并创建一个新的快捷方式
with a signed trust that was in quotes
使用引号中的已签名信任
and you will never more experience UAC
你永远不会有更多的经验UAC
prompts for that shortcut also keep in
提示该快捷方式也会保留
mind to start the background service as
介意开始后台服务
a pop-up will notify at when
弹出窗口会在何时通知
a start-up very important to keep in
一个非常重要的初创企业
mind so you can download that from IT
介意你可以从IT下载它
knowledge 24.com okay and that's it I
知识24.com 好吧，就是 我
have a nice time and have a nice day
祝你玩得愉快，度过愉快的一天
Robbie by Philly or Philip haha thanks
罗比由费城或菲利普哈哈谢谢
Phillip Philly here you're not revision
Phillip Philly在这里你没有修改
UAC well that's why I correct myself
UAC这就是我纠正自己的原因
Universal I realized it was nice no
环球我意识到这很 不错
accessibility keep going universal
可访问性继续普及
access no the user access control okay
访问没有用户访问控制没关系
I'm windows 7 wasn't even close and
我的Windows 7甚至还没有接近和
Windows Vista but nobody nobody cares on
Windows Vista但没有人关心
Windows 7 you're going to get these
Windows 7你会得到这些
prompts and I've got an application here
提示，我在这里有一个申请
I'm going to give that a try because one
我要尝试一下，因为一个
of our broadcast tools constantly asked
我们的广播工具不断被问到
me and even planet calypso same thing
我，甚至行星calypso同样的事情
always at its not planet calypso it's
总是在它的行星calypso它
windows user access control is it
Windows用户访问控制就是它
prompts you and says d are you sure you
提示你，说你确定你
want to allow this it's microsoft's wave
想要允许这是微软的浪潮
rubbin of wiping their hands of any
任何擦手的rubbin
damage that you caused to your computer
您对计算机造成的损害
by running applications that you said
通过运行您说的应用程序
okay right rather than actually create a
好吧，而 不是实际创建一个
secure OS they just say let's put the
安全的操作系统，他们只是说让我们把它
onus on the on the user are you sure are
关于用户的责任你确定是
you sure you want to do that well you
你确定要做到 这一点，那么您
said yes so it's your fault if you break
是的，所以 如果你休息 ，这是你的 错
it but it gets annoying when you've got
它，但你得到它会很烦人
applications that's why you don't want
应用程序，这就是你不想要的原因
to turn off UAC because if you do you're
关闭UAC是因为如果你这样做的话
basically allowing any application to do
基本上允许任何应用程序
stuff on your system that you probably
你可能在你的系统上的东西
don't want it to have access to do
不希望它有权 访问
that's where viruses and malware and
这就是病毒和恶意软件的地方
fake virus scanners that slow your
假病毒扫描程序会减慢您的速度
system down we're all these those kinds
系统下来我们都是这些
of things get into your system gad will
东西进入你的系统将GAD
mentioning that they they think that
提到他们认为那样
it's more like trying to emulate the
它更像是试图效仿
privilege raising such as Linux and UNIX
特权提升，如Linux和UNIX
does and I think it's that emulate is
是的，我认为仿效是
the key word but it is you know there's
关键词，但它是你知道的
that it still it puts the responsibility
它仍然承担责任
on the user so by disabling UAC you're
对用户而言，通过禁用UAC就可以了
basically effectively saying okay
基本上有效地说好了
anything that wants to install itself on
任何想要自己安装的东西
my computer no matter whether I
我的电脑，不管我
proof of it or not is going to be
证明它与否
allowed and you don't want to do that on
允许，你不想这样做
your Windows system because that's very
你的Windows系统，因为它非常
dangerous so using a tool like like was
危险因此使用类似的工具
just suggested that's a great
刚刚建议这很棒
opportunity for you to be able to
机会你能为
disable that prompt on specific
在特定情况下禁用该提示
application so that when I bring up plan
申请时，我提出计划
a Calypso I don't have to say yes I give
一个Calypso我不必说是的，我给
this one access every single time yes it
这一次每次访问是的
could be you look like you're doing some
可能你看起来像是在做一些事情
pretty heavy stuff on you can be taking
你可以采取相当沉重的东西
our bandwidth here normally closed that
我们的带宽通常在那里关闭
down if you could you didn't want me to
如果你能不能让我这么做的话
google ok ok durable save that for after
google ok ok耐用保存，以后
the show he's got like this big fancy
这个节目他有这么大的幻想
flash website and it's like everyone's
Flash网站，就像每个人一样
like why is the feed all of a sudden
喜欢为什么突然喂食
stuttering you should pull in like 800
口吃，你应该像800一样拉
kilobits a second I think that's a
一秒钟我觉得这是一个
little harsh yeah yeah we'll look it up
有点苛刻是啊是的我们会查找它
after the show that's David fine ah yes
演出结束后，大卫很好啊是的
ok let's take a look at the GIMP GNU
好的， 让我们来看看GIMP GNU
image manipulation program we've got
我们得到的图像处理程序
just about 12 minutes left to the show
距离演出约12分钟
so I'm going to pull up I'm going to
所以我要去拉起我要去
pull up a thumbnail from last week's
拉上上周的缩略图
episode let's just to show you that this
我只是为了告诉你这一集
well I've mentioned it before any time I
我在任何时候都提到过它
do these basic photo manipulation
做这些基本的照片操作
techniques using free software in that
使用自由软件的技术
series I'm giving you knowledge of how
系列我告诉你如何知识
to do certain things I'm not saying this
做某些事我不是说这个
is exactly how you want to do it or take
正是你想要的方式或采取
this image and turn it into this I'm
这个图像，把它变成我的
basically given arming you with some
基本上给你一些武装你
techniques and some and some abilities
技巧和一些能力
so that when it comes down to actually
所以，当它 归结为实际
doing something that that you do need to
做的事情，你需要
do you say oh yeah I remember how to do
你说哦是的我记得怎么办
this from such-and-such whichever
这是从这样的，以此为准
episode of what so my hope is that
我的希望就是这样的一集
something about that you'll learn along
关于你将要学习的东西
the way is going to be useful for you
这种方式对你有用
and if you follow along if you give
如果你坚持下去
these things a try then the
这些东西一试即可
the skills that you're going to gain
你将获得的技能
from it is going to be very helpful i'm
来自它将是非常有帮助的我
sure so let's let's pick a thumbnail
当然，让我们选择一个缩略图
here I've got a handful of pictures from
我在这里收到了一些照片
last week's episode every week we get a
上周我们每周都有一集
folder spewed out of images from our
文件夹从我们的图像喷出
broadcasting system so i can just
广播系统这样我就可以
basically grab any one of these photos
基本上抓住这些照片中的任何一张
open it up into the gimp there we go
我们去那里打开它进入gimp
looks good so to create a button what i
看起来很好所以创建一个按钮我
want to do is now this is going to be
想要做的就是现在这将是
like the universal button technique
像通用按钮技术
using a glossy button so what I'm going
使用光滑的按钮，所以我要去
to do is I'm going to take this first of
要做的是我要先拿这个
all I want to crop it out so that it's
所有我想把它裁剪出去以便它
kind of a button shape and a button
一种按钮形状和一个按钮
sighs and it doesn't have the ticker at
感叹，它没有自动收报机
the bottom there so I've grabbed my
那里的底部所以我抓住了我的
rectangular marquee here rectangle
这里的矩形字幕矩形
select and I've clicked into my image
选择，我点击了我的图像
and created a square not a square but a
并且创建了一个方形而不是方形但是一个
regular go mingle thank you and then I'm
定期去混合，谢谢你，然后我
i can adjust with the gimp you can
我可以用gimp调整你
adjust the marquee which is a very handy
调整一个非常方便的选框
thing to be able to do and now what I'm
能够做的事情，现在我能做什么
going to do is I'm going to right click
要做的是我要点击右键
on that image and I'm going to go image
在那张图片上，我要去拍照
crop to selection that's going to get
裁剪到将要获得的选择
rid of everything that's outside of that
摆脱那些外面 的 东西
Markie so now as we look at that that's
Markie现在我们正在看那个
what our image looks like so that's
我们的形象是什么样的
slowly isn't that fantastic first thing
慢慢不是第一件事
I want to do is I want to clean up the
我想做的 是 我要清理
image I'm going to duplicate the layer
image我要复制图层
make it look a little sharper I'm going
让它看起来更清晰我要走了
to go right clicking filters everything
右键单击筛选所有内容
is in right clicks on the GIMP I'm going
正在点击我正在进行的GIMP
to go blur Gaussian blur and I'm going
去模糊高斯模糊，我要去
to just give it that little subtle bit
只是给它那个微妙的位
of a blur so that now it's a little bit
一个模糊，所以现在它有点
blurry if you look at the image close up
如果你近距离观察图像会很模糊
I'm going to change the mode to probably
我打算将模式改为
a hard light just a kind of darken it
强光只是一种变暗
and give it some there's the original
并给它一些原始的
there's hard light kind of gives it more
有强烈的光线让它更多
of a film look to it now I'm going to
一部电影看起来我现在要去
grab this tool up here our paths tool
抓住这个工具我们的路径工具
now you know me Eric that I don't I
现在你认识我埃里克，我不是
don't work in vector at all you're not
你根本不在矢量中工作
the vector it's not a vector guy because
矢量它不是矢量人因为
I never have been good at it I'm not an
我从来没有擅长过它我不是一个
artist I
艺术家我
so I don't really do any of that because
所以我 并没有真正做到这一点，因为
artists but i will use the path tool to
艺术家，但我将使用路径工具
do this i'm single clicked one area i'm
这样我单击一个区域就可以了
going to go about halfway through the
要走了一半
image okay and notice a little bit of an
形象好，注意 的 一点
angle and now i'm going to click outside
角度，现在我要点击外面
of the image here and hold and drag and
这里的图像，并按住并拖动
see what I'm getting there so you can
看看我到那里，你可以
get these kind of effects right and you
得到这些效果和你
can change your curve and you get this
可以改变你的曲线，你就明白了
this beautiful nice curve you can move
你可以移动这条美丽漂亮的曲线
it around and then you can complete the
它周围然后你可以完成
curve by going around the outside and
环绕外面的曲线
then once you've got everything there i
一旦你掌握了一切，我就会
can hit enter and it creates this
可以点击进入，它会创建这个
marquee inside of that area so now if i
那个区域内的大帐篷所以现在如果我
right click and go layer new layer and
右键单击并转到图层新图层
just a transparent layer and i
只是一个透明的层和我
right-click a game they go edit fill
右键单击他们编辑填充的游戏
with anything it's black you'll see that
什么都是黑色你会看到
now if i get rid of the marquee it's got
现在，如果我摆脱了它的大帐篷
this black area there okay so now i'm
这个黑色区域还可以，所以现在我
going to use the because I filled that
打算使用，因为我填写了
black I'm going to turn on my lair lock
黑色我要打开我的巢穴锁
here the Alpha lock okay on that layer
这里的Alpha锁在那层上没问题
and I'm going to change my colors to
我要改变颜色了
like a gray I've done this by clicking
像灰色一样，我通过点击完成了这个
on my color here and the other one can
在我的颜色和另一个可以
be white as it is and I'm going to grab
是白色的，我要 抓住
my gradient tool
我的渐变工具
where are you do they call it a blend
你在哪里做，他们称之为混合
tool yeah it is they call it a blend
工具是的，他们称之为混合物
tool in the GIMP so now i'm going to
在GIMP工具所以现在我要去
highlight there and see what i can do
突出显示那里，看看我能做些什么
I'm only filling that curve that I
我只填充那条曲线
created okay now if I change the opacity
如果 我改变不透明度， 现在创建好 了
of that layer bring it down you'll see
你会看到那层下来
what it ends up looking like is that
最终看起来像是什么
little bit of a gloss yeah very cool
有点光泽，非常酷
kind of a neat effect that yeah it there
那是一种整洁的效果，是的
and it seems like such a subtle thing
它看起来像是一件微妙的事情
but all of a sudden starts to look like
但突然间看起来像
this kind of beveled looking button next
接下来是这种斜面看的按钮
step is I'm going to hit my square
一步是我要去我的广场
marquee and again because we're working
另外， 因为我们正在工作
in layers remember you can always turn
分层记住，你总是可以转身
off that layer if you're not happy with
如果你不满意那就离开那一层
it and start a game just create a new
它开始游戏只是创造一个新的
layer and go again I think that looks
层，然后再去我认为 看起来
fine I got a nice looking curve there
很好，我在那里有一个漂亮的曲线
but you cannot you can experiment so now
但你现在不能实验
i'm going to have got my marquee here
我要在这里拿到我的大帐篷
again square i'm going to click anywhere
再次正方形我要点击任何地方
and go control a I've selected all
并控制 我已经选择了所有
you'll see that the Marquis is going
你会看到侯爵要去了
around the entire image okay i'm going
在整个图像周围好吗 我要去
to right click actually i'll zoom in a
点击右键实际上我将在放大
little bit so you can see i'm going to
点点，所以你可以看到我要去
right click with everything selected I'm
右键单击所选的一切我是
going to go select shrink I guess select
去选择缩小我猜选择
how many pixels of a board or do I want
一块板的像素数或我想要的数量
i'm going to say on over and it put me
我要说完了，它把我放了
an image of this size let's say 10 so
这个尺寸的图像让我们说10个
now you'll see what that did is because
现在你会看到它的作用是因为
it's shrunk my selection it's actually
它缩小了我的选择它实际上
brought that in 10 pixels from each edge
从每个边缘带来10个像素
so it's got a perfect border i'm going
所以它有一个完美的边界我要去
to right click and go select invert and
右键单击并选择反转和
now it's just the border that's selected
现在它只是选择的边界
okay so now i'm going to create another
好的，所以现在我要 创造另一个
new layer this is going to be my border
新层这将是我的边界
which is going to end up looking like a
这将最终看起来像一个
bevel and I got create a transparent
斜角，我创造了一个透明的
layer I'm going to fill that with white
我将用白色填充它
which is my background color so now I've
这是我的背景颜色，所以现在我
got this white border around the entire
整个周围都有这个白色边框
image
图片
so if I turn everything else off you can
所以，如果我关掉其他一切，你可以
see that's the border ok so now to give
看到这是好的边界，现在给予
it that beveled look you know what we
它倾斜看你知道我们是什么
need to do is we need to create like a
我们需要做的就是创造一个像
shadow on the on the lower portion of
阴影在下半部分
that so what I'm going to do is I'm
所以我要做的就是我
going to grab this marquee tool up here
要在这里抓住这个选框工具
that looks like a lass ooh ok it's
看起来像个小姑娘哦 好吧
called free select in the GIMP sometimes
有时在GIMP中称为自由选择
my zoom throws me across the screen
我的缩放让我穿过屏幕
sorry about that so now going to go over
对不起，所以现在要过去了
here to the top right corner and I'm
在这里右上角，我
going to click as close to the point as
要点击尽可能接近点
I can there goes my zoom acting silly
我可以让我的变焦行为愚蠢
again okay i'm going to try again click
再好吧我打算再试一次点击
and then see how I've got the line
然后看看我是如何得到这条线的
that's my marquee that's where is going
那是我的选择，这就是我要去的地方
to put my mark ii i'm going to put that
把我的标记给我，我会把它
so that it's a straight line from corner
这是从角落的直线
to corner see that ok i'm going to take
到角落里看到好的， 我要 带
it down to this corner and i'm going to
下来到这个角落 ，我要去
click i'm going to take it right into
点击我 要把它带进去
the corner so that it's a nice perfect
角落，这是一个很好的完美
corner now going to go all the way
角落现在一路走了
around the image so now what is selected
在图像周围，所以现在选择什么
is half exactly half of that border so
是那个边界的一半
now again we're going to have to turn on
现在我们将不得不打开
our lock transparency because we only
我们的锁透明度，因为我们只
want to fill that one part and we're
我想填补那一部分
going to use that gray that I've done in
打算用 我做过的 灰色
my foreground I'm going to go edit fill
我的前景我 要去编辑填充
with foreground color and now you'll see
与前景色，现在你会看到
that that portion within the marquee is
在选框内的那个部分是
a darker gray because I've got locked my
一个更深的灰色，因为我锁定了我的
transparent if that was turned off this
透明，如果关闭这个
is what would happen if I filled it
如果我填写它 会 发生什么
let's see here
让我们看看这里
Phil foreground see what happens there
菲尔前景看看那里发生了什么
looks much different thing so by having
通过拥有看起来很不一样的东西
the lock alpha layer turned on I get
锁定alpha图层打开我得到
that so deselect and I end up with this
这样取消选择，我最终得到了这个
nice-looking beveled image with the nice
漂亮的斜面图像
kind of button looking thing at the top
一种按钮在顶部看东西
so that works with pretty much any image
所以适用于任何图像
and you can do that with you know if you
如果你知道的话 ， 你就可以 知道
want to create buttons if you want to
想要创建按钮
create will be using a similar kind of
创建将使用类似的
effect for our new website with any of
对我们的新网站的任何影响
the player windows if you want to click
如果你想点击播放器窗口
play on the images like on the video
播放视频上的图像
that's what it's going to it's going to
这就是它将会发生的事情
have some kind of similar effect to that
有一些类似的效果
so that's a very basic and yet kind of
所以这是一个非常基本但又有点的
funky effect burdens and I'll call that
时髦的效果负担，我会称之为
the Glaus buttons from basic photo
基本照片中的Glaus按钮
manipulation using free software that's
使用免费软件进行操作
GNU image manipulation program available
GNU图像处理程序可用
for free download for Windows Mac and
免费下载Windows Mac和
Linux at gimp.org and will of course
Linux在gimp.org，当然会
have links in the show notes for episode
在剧集的节目笔记中有链接
number 160 a great little program
160号是一个很棒的小程序
actually there's really no differences
实际上确实没有差异
between the windows version in the are
在 是 Windows版本之间
there yeah there but there by certain
是的，但是确实存在
they're they're both very similar and do
他们是非常相似的
a great job and sometimes I get because
一个伟大的工作，有时我得到因为
i use both photoshop and again depending
我同时使用Photoshop和Photoshop
on the application so so that's why
在应用程序上所以这就是原因
sometimes I forget that you know what
有时我会忘记你知道什么
the tools are called or whatever but we
除了我们之外，还可以调用这些工具
get the weekend right impression right
获得周末正确的印象吧
so but that said because I'm so versed
所以，但那说，因为我很精通
in both Photoshop and the GIMP I can see
在Photoshop和GIMP中我都能看到
where we can we can do these things in
我们可以在哪里做这些事情
either Photoshop or GIMP so we don't
Photoshop或GIMP，所以我们不这样做
need to spend a thousand dollars to do
需要 花一千美元来做
this kind of an effect so that's a nice
这种效果让人感觉很好
that's a nice thing next word
这是一件很好的事一个字
we're just about at a time no way yeah
我们只是在一个时间没有办法，是的
are you eating well I just got Twitter
你吃得好我刚拿到 推特
up in everything Molly the other didn't
在所有的莫莉，另一个没有
want to use it while you're brainless
想要在你没脑子的时候使用它
twit all you won't do it using Twitter
所有你不会使用Twitter做到这一点
you might do it looking at a website
你可能会看一个网站
that streaming videos done through was
流媒体视频完成了
she was bad attitude totally totally I
她完全是我态度恶劣的态度
was just checking out some suggestions
刚刚查看了一些建议
filmer I came from our friend Peter
我来自我们的朋友彼得
Lewis but i'll have to check that out
刘易斯，但我必须检查出来
another time with all the the changes
所有变化的另一次
that we're making the show over the next
我们正在制作这个节目
over the next month or so with the
在接下来的一个月左右
quality with we're going to be upgrading
质量我们将要升级
our software we're going to wire cast
我们的软件我们将用线
for and we're going to be reviewing that
因为，我们将审查这一点
software very very soon very excited but
软件非常非常非常兴奋但是
i would ask that hey pop me an email pop
我会问 ，嘿，给我一个电子邮件流行音乐
me a viewer testimonial let me know what
我的观众见证让我知道
you think of of the quality of the show
你想到了节目的质量
if something has changed if if things
如果事情发生了变化
are working better or worse for you we
我们正在为你做得更好或更糟
want to hear about it this is your show
想听听这是你的节目
and we'd love to you know we want to
我们爱你，你知道 我们想要的
make this as good as we can for you and
尽我们所能为您和您做好准备
certainly you know that said get your
当然你知道说得到你的
questions in the way that you can
你可以提出的问题
control the content of the show if
控制节目的内容如果
you're watching this you're saying oh
你在看这个你说的哦
this is way over my head or this is
这是我的头脑或这是
really you know this is way below me or
真的，你知道这是在我或以下
whatever that's how you control the show
无论 你 如何 控制节目
is get your questions in pop me an email
是给你的问题给我一个电子邮件
live at category 5 TV and you will have
住在5类电视，你会有
control over the content does everything
控制内容可以做到一切
look 3dp right now it does um sorry
现在看看3dp它对不起
nevermind that's his random to sense
没关系，这是他随意的感觉
where we haven't this is wild
我们没有他妈的这是疯狂的
good times good time good time all right
美好的时光美好时光的好时机没事
that's it that's all right that's all
就是这样就可以了
the time we have here hey we'll see you
我们在这里的时间嘿，我们会见到你
next Tuesday night nice to have you here
下周二晚很高兴你能来这里
tonight and DuPont me an email again
今晚和杜邦再次给我发了一封电子邮件
live at category 5 TV papas a viewer
住在5类电视节目的观众
testimonial at category 5 TV click on
第5类电视的推荐点击
interact submit a testimonial and don't
互动提交推荐书而不是
forget we have that printer to give away
忘了我们有那台打印机放弃
it's a multi-function Center from
它是一个多功能中心
Brother Canada and you'll find out how
兄弟加拿大，你会发现如何
you can qualify by clicking on the
你可以通过点击来获得资格
interact menu at category five dot TV
五类点电视的互动菜单
you'll be able to follow the links and
你将能够按照链接和
check out the printer as well so do that
检查打印机也这样做
this week and we'll talk
本周我们会谈
next Tuesday night for episode number
下周二晚上的剧集编号
169 all right good night kids take care
169正确的晚安孩子要小心
now children good night Robby see ya
现在孩子们晚安罗比见到了你